One Dream,
oh.
Thank you.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Oh, that's a cop!
So, why were those guys
coming after you anyway?
I'll tell you.
I was on my way to the market to
help with some shopping when those
big mean men with a giant baboon
spotted me and tried to hurt me.
That's when Komatsu jumped
in to save me from them.
Oh, so that's why you
two were fighting then.
But that's not all.
They stole everything I had on me.
I got real, real mad and I said
something that was against the law.
The Kozuki clan has got to
go back and then you'll be!
What was that?
Let go of me!
You know, if it worked for you, I'd
probably still be with those awful jerks.
and I'd never see my home again.
I owe you one for helping
me, so thanks a lot.
Now let me do a favor for you too, okay?
That would be great.
I got a bunch of questions you could
answer for me since I just got here.
I get it.
Bet you're hungry, aren't ya?
You think this is good?
Should be perfect.
No bad guys will find
your ship if it's in here.
Tang.
I'm out of food.
Don't worry.
I know what to do, big brother.
Come to my place!
I'll pay you back by
feeding you dinner, okay?
Komachiyo! Make proud! Let's go!
You too, Hihimaru!
How did you come up
with that name for him?
He just looked like one to me! Gotcha!
Lead the way, Hihimaru!
You know,
I met a bunch of pirates
and I like the good ones,
but there's some bad ones I don't like.
Oh, yeah?
You say so.
I know I'm gonna like you
because you're strong and nice.
That's my house just up ahead!
So you live in a village on the mountains?
No, it's not there anymore.
My master and I live all by ourselves now.
Know what?
When I grow up, I'm gonna be so tough!
A real bewitching ninja!
Bewitching?
It's kind of stinky and cramped in here.
Hey, that's awfully rude, big bro.
That's starting to smell good.
Hang tight, it's almost ready.
Oh, much longer, Dome!
The rice is finally done!
Here you go!
Fluffy, hot, and fresh out of the pot!
Eat up, Big Bro!
Huh?
This rice is all for me?
Down the hatch!
It's yummy!
Hey, Thelma, you eating?
Nah, I'm okay!
Plus, Pimichi can't be fast
if they have a full belly!
Can I have another?
It's gone?
That was all I had, so there's
no more rice left. What?
As for pickles, I'm out too.
That's okay.
Hey, I was only joking anyway.
Huh?
You're a bad liar!
I gotta run to the party!
I didn't get full on that, but it was
pretty nice of her to make me food.
That Tama girl is all right.
You don't belong here.
Who are you?
Wait, who's up?
No, you're not!
Why are you sprawled out on my floor?
Don't tell me...
You ate the rice, didn't you?
I did?
Who are you?
Why, you imbecile!
Stop gurgling, Tobi!
How shameful!
Wait a sec!
Can we top this over?
I mean, all I did was eat the bowl
of rice that Tama cooked for me.
She made you food?
Why in the world would she do that?
Do you know how many days it's been
since she's had even a bite to eat?
Well, that poor girl weaves
hats day in and day out.
And if she's lucky, she'll
sell the whole batch,
earning her just enough money to
barely get by and feed herself.
Most
of
the time,
she's forced to eat millet and...
And that's if she's lucky.
But that is not the tragic part.
She only gets rice twice a year
for New Year's and her birthday.
I sent her to the market today.
Because she was to buy
herself a sack of rice?
for her eighth birthday.
You consume that poor girl's only meal.
Master!
Please don't be mad!
I know I cooked the rice
without asking first!
I'm sorry!
I shouldn't have, but I wanted
to repay the man who saved me!
But please don't yell at him,
I was the one who did it!
I promise to weave more
hat to make it up to you!
Try to understand!
I owe my life to Big Bro Luffy.
I just wanted to repay him.
Please.
Oh Tama.
Tama.
Are you okay?
You were foolish, girl You filled
up on river water, didn't you?
To ease your hunger pangs She what?
It's unfortunate.
But the waters of this land are polluted
by runoff waste from Kaido's factory.
For such a small and
frail girl as herself,
drinking it is no different
than drinking straight poison.
Why are you guys living in
such a run-down place then?
It's complicated.
There are safer places she could live.
But she has chosen to stay here.
She's waiting for a man
who promised he'd return.
He is a pirate who goes by the name Ace.
Tama.
This ace you're waiting
for, his full name, it's...
Port Gusti Ace.
Isn't it?
Are you saying you know him too?
Really, Big Bro?
Yeah.
But he's dead now.
That's a lie, Big Bro!
You liar!
Big Bro, you are a liar!
Tama! Tama! Otama!
Tama, you have to calm down!
Looks like she fainted.
That's crazy.
So my brother came to Wano, too?
What kind of devil are you?
How could you just casually tell
poor little Otama that Ace died?
But it's true, though.
Even if it is the truth, that wasn't
the proper way to inform her! Okay.
She should know sooner than later.
Be that as it may, you should have
considered how and when to say it.
have you no concept of delicacy
just who in the hell are you
anyway boy my name's Luffy and
I'll be king of the pirates pirate
state show business here I like
precious few pirates why not
say who you are fine then my name
is he tests you the Swordsmith.
Since you know Ace is gone now,
you should get out of here.
Take Tama and move somewhere better.
I have no greater desire than to do that.
Believe you me.
But I, too, have been awaiting
someone for quite some time.
There are only two of us now.
But this was once a
village called Amigasa.
Around a year ago,
our peaceful little home was attacked by
one of Kaido's newly recruited headliners.
A pirate by the name of Diaz Drake.
The five samurai who protected our
territory were soundly defeated.
Our buildings were destroyed.
Presently, there's only one place in
the land of Wano that still flourishes.
The flower capital, where
the shogun orgy resides.
Everywhere else has been
reduced to a lawless
wilderness by the wicked acts
of Kaido and his followers.
That fiend came here four years ago.
The people who lived here never had much,
so when they took away what little we
had, many of us succumbed to starvation.
But then, when all seemed lost,
Ace washed up ashore on our beach.
Our villagers tied up
all the weakened pirates
and consumed their food
and water supplies.
We were desperate.
It was our only means of survival.
But once we devoured everything,
to our surprise, Ace easily
broke out of his restraints.
We feared what retribution
laid in wait for us.
You get enough to eat, kid?
Good.
I bet you want dessert then, huh?
So tell me, fellas.
Where can I score some cake?
Stay put.
I'll go find us something.
We were all utterly stunned.
Ace and his crew ended up staying
with us for several weeks.
Otama grew particularly
fond of the young pirate.
It's still hard for me to believe how
alive saved by shipwrecked pirates.
Yeah.
That's him.
Hey!
Where can I get some food and water? Huh?
and do you guys have
a doctor around here a
doctor i want to take
tama to one i owe her for
feeding me imbecile get
back here your outfit is
too outlandish and draw
attention and put this on.
Nice, a kimono.
Hey, stop squirming around.
Do I get to wear sweet samurai armor, too?
You're trying not to draw attention.
This isn't a war.
That should do it.
I cannot join you for reasons of my own.
Please, protect her.
Whatever costs you incur,
I shall reimburse you.
Guess we'll see.
If we run into my crew, I'm sure
they'll be happy to help you for free.
So keep your fingers crossed.
Whatcha got there?
It's cool if I borrow this, right?
Really sells the look.
Well, see ya.
Just hang on, Tama.
I'll get you help.
Wait! Come back!
You can't take that, you fool.
It's disrespectful to even look
at that blade without reverence.
It's an heirloom forged by my forefather,
the renowned swordsmith Kitetsu.
It's one of only 21
excellent great swords.
That blade you hold is Kitetsu II.
Heed well.
Among the innumerable swords of the world,
only a few are so finely crafted
as to be called grade blades.
The most superb are grouped into classes.
There are 50 fine grade,
21 excellent grade, and lastly,
12 supreme grade blades.
Kittetsu, in particular, has
a rich folklore behind it.
He's gone!
I'm taking it!
See you later! Wait!
I wasn't finished!
I said wait!
Stop!
I forbid it!
Fine, then give me that one at least!
This one is a famed blade as well!
The one you seized is cursed!
Truly a ghastly thing!
You don't want to heal that!
Whoever does will face
misfortune, for sure!
See you later, Grandpa Nose!
Do not let anything happen
to Otama or so help me!
I'll take good care of her.
You better return the blade as well!
Are you listening?
He isn't listening.
It's the giant puppy.
Can we hitch a ride on you?
Heck yeah Yeah!
Spine taking us to town, pal?
Hey, Tama!
Finally awake? Big bro!
Where's Komachiyo taking us?
To the doctor!
Do you think your dog knows the way there?
But Ace is dead now.
Whoa, whoa!
Knock it off, Tama, or you're gonna fall!
Yeah!
You're a big old liar!
I'm sorry, but Ace is gone.
Ask anyone.
We all know what happened in Marineford.
It can't be!
We made a promise, and I know
Ace wouldn't break his life.
Ace, take me with you on your ship.
I'm big enough to go.
But you're only five. Sorry, kid.
So, I'll be six next year.
You're getting good at that.
Of course I am.
You're going to leave
soon, aren't you? Uh-huh.
I got a few things to take care of, okay?
I don't want you to go.
I want you guys all to stay.
Tama.
I won't keep you waiting too long.
We'll come back soon and
with a much bigger crew.
Then if I wait, can I join
you after you come back?
I want to sail and go on
an adventure with you guys.
Look, a pirate's got to be strong.
But I'll tell you what?
When I come back, if you become a
bewitching ninja, I promise to take you.
Now that's cute!
Funny choice of words, though?
Okay, then!
Do you really promise?
No taxis-paxis, okay?
Please.
He was so kind to me.
It's not fair.
I waited so long for him.
Oh, he was so nice!
You don't know how much you've missed!
You will never understand my fate!
And it hurts!
Quit hitting me!
You're a big Fight!
You don't care at all!
You're no big pro!
You're just a chick!
That's the end of the forest!
Grimpa knows what's right.
It's not a joke.
It really is a wasteland.
A tiger!
And the big boar, too!
What's that thing?
Oh, that's a shark-o-dial!
This place is wild!
Just eat those guys, then
you won't be so hungry!
It's not that easy.
All the samurai who
were powerful enough to
take them down were either
caught by the police.
or they turned into bandits to survive.
Besides...
Animals around here drink
the polluted river water.
Because of that, they become
way too poisonous for us to eat.
But they look so meaty and tasty!
It's unforgivable!
Is that the factory making all the smoke?
Yeah, that's right!
They make weapons and
they have a mine there!
And that's not all!
That place is full of bad
guys that work! Kaido!
Well, what do they eat then?
The Shogun and Kaido have a farm.
No one else can use it.
It makes food just for them.
They have clean water, and rice
fields, and veggies, and fish too.
Plus a lot of food.
I gotcha.
So they do have food around here.
Tama, you okay?
Talk to me!
Oh, no.
I think your fever's getting even worse.
Just hang on, okay?
I'll get you to a doctor.
If those jerks have enough food and
water, then I'll make this work.
Hurry it up, dog!
Please show mercy on me!
You can't outrun us.
Drop everything you've got, lady.
I beg of you!
Someone help!
you bastard i'll make you pay
stay back i'll handle this
I know that face.
This is Orochillo.
What you got there?
Looks like sake.
Give it here!
My lord, Samurai! Yeah.
Huh?
Good, sir.
Whoever you are, thank you for saving me.
I owe you my life.
Woo!
Stand up. No big deal.
I was just after that
bozo's jug of sake anyway.
I mean, honorably speaking.
But surely I can repay you somehow.
Hmm.
More sake!
I don't have any on my person.
Zoro!
Hey, Zoro! It's me!
Over here!
Luffy, yeah!
You finally made it!
It's real good to see you!
It's been a while!
It's been a long time,
most honorable Zoro!
Is everyone with you?
Yeah, but we got split up.
They're okay.
Whoa, I smell meat!
Give me a snack!
There are so many fish and animals around
here, you would not believe it, Luffy.
Here you go.
This area has so much to hunt.
No, be careful.
The water in this place is
poisonous and the wildlife drink it.
So if you got this off an animal
here, then it's poison too.
Checks out.
Guess that's why my stomach hurts.
Anyway, Zoro, we should
probably get going now!
I ran into this little girl.
One thing led to another.
And now I need to take her to a doctor.
She's not feeling good.
Oh, yeah.
The brat's in rough shape.
Why the heck are you
stopping to eat, then?
It'll be okay.
I'll be done in a sec.
Just choke it down already. I'm crying.
Hello, gentlemen.
How fortunate that I found the
fugitive Ronin himself, Zoro Giri.
and he brought companions
wait a
minute
we know him yeah be careful seems like.
he's working for Kaido Straw Hat is here.
I was just on my way to Kuri Beach I.
I presume you're the culprit
behind the shoreline assault.
I was told I lost two
subordinates in one baboon.
The likelihood that you were
behind the attack is 98%.
However, that does not matter now.
In the land of Wano, you
must choose your path.
Follow the strong, or become their prey.
I think we're about to piss
Kin'emon off, huh, Luffy?
He warned us not to make a scene.
Uh-huh, well, too bad.
I'll apologize later.